They need electricity from the dam...
(Penny(to Kevin):)...but at the same time,
they wanna preserve the environment.
(Leonard:)You're kidding me.
(Leonard:)- Uh, can I see you for a sec over here?
- Oh, sure. Just one sec?
(Man:)No problem.
- What's up?
- I know what you're doing.
(Leonard:)- What?
- You're going to talk to that guy...
(Leonard:)- ...because I said we weren't on a date.
- I'm talking to him because he's cute.
- Uh, come on. He's not that cute.
- Yes, he is...
(Penny:)...with his dorky T-shirt
and his little hipster glasses.
(Leonard:)I wear dorky T-shirts and glasses.
(Penny:)Yes, but when you're tall and have great
cheekbones, you're doing it ironically.
(Leonard:)- So, what if I start talking to a girl?
- You should.
- Yeah, heh. I'm serious, I'll do it.
- Good, go.
There's some girls right over there.